Sand hospitals and video.
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky,
I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Come on, let's go,
everybody, we share the music,
Come on, let's go, baby, baby,
we share the one dream, Come
on, let's go, everybody,
we share the good time,
Come on, let's go, baby,
baby, we share, Oh, we
share the one world,
It's hard to see for you and me, Through
the darkness that is in this world,
So hard to see, but to believe,
In where we need to go, Yes,
you and me, it's true that we, Feel
the rush brought on by this world,
Through head to feet, I feel
the beat, Getting me to walk on,
oh yeah, Share the music, no matter what,
Share the one dream, believe in yourself,
Share the good times, take my
hand now, Share the one world now,
I look up to the stars, And reach
for the sky, No matter what,
I'll try no matter how
high, So let us go, beyond,
far and wide, I believe
in tomorrow if we try,
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Come on, let's
go, everybody, Oh, we share the music,
We share the music, Come on, let's go,
baby, baby, Oh, we share the one world, Oh,
as we chase, we're being
chased, From the top we go,
one straight and wild, We're on
our way, I've got to say, Hey,
I want to share your style, Now
here it starts, so don't lose heart,
They're bound to lose to this
flavor, From boot to hood,
I feel so good, I will be free
to be, oh yeah, Share the music,
even if I, Share the one
dream, I know where you are,
Share the times, share the one world now,
I look up to the stars, And reach
for the sky, No matter what,
I'll try no matter how high, So let us go,
beyond, far and wide, I
believe in tomorrow if we try,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know that
you are there, Just on the other side,
Wait there for me, Soon it will be
you and I, Then let us go, beyond,
far and wide, I believe in
the one world if we try,
Come on, let's go, maybe, maybe,
Oh, we share the one world,
The flying fish just left?
And they were the ones
who started the attack.
Weird.
It seemed like they received a message.
Maybe it was an order for them to retreat.
I can't imagine why, though.
Those flying fish are cool.
I want to ride one.
They can stay in the air
for five minutes, right?
That's five minutes of awesome for me.
We're headed to their base now, so
we'll see them again soon enough.
We better be careful, though.
It might not be so easy next time.
At least we know they can
attack from the sea or the air.
Hey, how about lining
the deck with cannons?
Sniper Usopp will blow him out of the sky!
Good thinking, bro.
I'm worried.
I wonder if Hatchan is okay.
Worry about yourself
while you're at it, Kuma.
Mackerel wants to catch you bad.
Don't drop your guard.
Yeah, you're right.
Master Devil, the three
riders have returned!
I don't get it.
Why'd you ask us to call off the attack?
Yeah, what gives?
We could have captured the mermaids
and those pirates in one fell swoop.
Idiots.
Listen up,
I told you a million times
I want those pirates alive!
Cause I'm on ripping limb from
limb with my own two hands!
Whenever I start thinking about that guy?
It's like I got an itch on
my back I can't scratch!
And I swear it gets worse every time!
No, no, here comes the accent!
Every day I've cursed that man's name!
Every day my hate for him grows!
It burns!
Head, just calm down,
get a hold of yourself!
And now that bastard's coming
straight to my front door!
And I'm gonna kill it!
This day's gonna be perfect!
Even if it kills me!
You got that?
You understand?
Yes, I understand completely
We won't ruin it for you.
That's why you gotta
follow my orders to the T.
Because I'm gonna murder this punk,
and ain't nobody gonna get in my way.
Okay, head, whatever you want.
Hey, macro gang.
Yeah, what do you want?
What is it, Davy?
Wait, did you say Davy?
And you too, Totsweet.
Can't you show a little
more respect than that?
You need to learn some manners.
He said Davy, that's funny.
That's enough.
I'm so very sorry.
You were saying, Master Devil, sir?
Hey, boss, that masked guy talks funny.
Will you shut up already?
My most sincere apologies, Master.
These two are dumb as bricks.
Just ignore everything they say, and
I promise they'll get the job done.
You can run your stupid
fish mouths all day.
I don't care.
Far as I'm concerned, you're
my angels of good fortune.
I can't even begin to tell you how grateful
I am for our little arrangement here.
You can try.
I told you to shut up, Tamsui!
You can call it luck,
but thanks to you three,
I can finally meet the Straw Hat Pirates.
I'll get my revenge.
Then I can finally get my life back.
Nope, Straw Hat Pirates.
Uh, now who might they be exactly?
The Straw Hats?
It wasn't just my imagination.
No!
Now listen good.
That guy.
The one I gotta kill if
it's the last thing I do.
He's on that boat, I can feel it.
I can feel my hands around
his neck as we speak.
Head, your accent, you gotta calm down.
Man, he must really hate
the crap out of that guy.
I never thought I'd hear the name
Straw Hat Pirates way out here.
You, hey, big guy.
Ah, that's Master Devil
showing some damn respect.
You're saying Kuma has been
captured by the Straw Hat Pirates?
You?
This is bad, really bad.
Of all the people she could run into, and
they're all on their way here together?
So it would seem.
They'll arrive any time now.
But she didn't seem all
that captured to me.
Looked more like she turned
to those pirates for help.
Far as I can tell, it looked like
they were working together just fine.
Well, it doesn't matter who she brings.
In the end, they'll all be rounded up,
caught, and sold to the human shop.
Once they're here, they're history.
That's what you think those
Straw Hats are crazy strong.
Ew I'm in trouble I wonder if Nami's still
with them too I wonder
if she's still mad at me.
Well duh of course she would be I did all
those horrible things to
her when I was working
for Arlong if I don't hurry up and figure
out some way to escape
before they get here.
I'll get my butt kicked just as much
as these other guys I'm so screwed.
The Straw Hats are here finally the
time has come uh hey Macro yeah what
do you want how about You let me go
and I give you some octopus fritters
I can buy my own damn seafood what
kind of gun do You think I am did you
see him is he on the ship yes Head
he's there for sure all right then now?
Now that everything
appears to be in order,
I think it's time for you
to get what's coming to you.
From the looks of it, I bet that's
the Flying Fish Rider's base.
So Kami's friend Hodgkin is being
held somewhere around here, right?
I'll go in there and save him
before you know it, beautiful Kuma.
Thanks, you're the best, Sanjee-chin.
Hold on, guys.
Before you go, listen up.
Be careful out there, okay?
The macro gang have managed to
capture me over 30 times already.
You get captured way too often.
You get eaten too often, too.
That's weird.
How would anyone want to set
up their base way out of here?
Eh, who knows.
For an enemy base, it's sure quiet.
I've got a bad feeling.
Luffy, you sure about this?
Go straight ahead! Hey!
Should we at least go over
the plan again or something?
Hey! Hatchan!
Are you okay?
Hey, Mackro! Show yourself!
Give us Hachi back!
That's their flag.
It really is the Straw Hats.
I've got to get out of here.
Damn, it's no use, I'm stuck.
That leaves me no choice.
Hachi, agent!
Am I seeing things, or is
something in that cage?
Is that...
it kind of looks like Hachi.
Oh, wow, we're in luck, Kuma.
There isn't a single enemy in sight.
Maybe they all decided that
this is snack time or something.
Probably.
You two cannot seriously be this stupid!
The blindest man in the
world could see that this
is a trap they're totally
hiding out waiting for us.
To investigate so they can ambush us what
a brilliant deduction
that's genius i never
would Have thought of that that's why you
dumbasses keep getting
caught you i'm here Kuma
i'm fine There's no
need to worry okay well
they didn't do that it's
my own fault actually
anyway this is A trap
get out of here before
they catch you don't worry i can take care
of myself i'll be Okay so just go there's
something about that
guy's voice that seems
really familiar you
noticed it too Right uh
-huh his shape too yeah
i know who he is you do
let's just ask him and get this over with
Already hey you so
how's arlong doing these
days huh oh not so good actually him chew
Caribou and all the others
got caught by the navy.
I was the only one who escaped.
Now I've given up my life of crime and
I'm running an octopus fritter shop.
Funny how time flies, right?
Arlong?
What an idiot.
It's you!
The dumb squid with the swords!
They treat me!
I'm right, aren't I?
You are one of Arlong's crew.
You're the octopus fritter guy?
What kind of crap is that? Arlong?
Yeah, it was a really long time ago.
Nami's hometown of Cocoyashi
Village used to be under the
control of a nasty bunch of
fishmen called the Arlong Pirates.
Nami herself was in an even worse
situation having to work for those jerks.
And this octopus guy, Hachi, was
one of Arlong's top henchmen.
So he's an old enemy, huh?
Well, he was.
But Luffy and I, mainly me,
came along and beat the crap out
of every last one of those guys.
Oh, wow!
Usopp, you're amazing!
Yeah, I know, right?
After we left the village,
I thought their whole crew was
going to get arrested by the Navy.
But it looks like this guy
left them behind and escaped.
I see.
Sounds like quite the ordeal.
Listen up, you dumb jerk fish!
Now that we know it's you, there's
no way we're going to save you,
so you better get used to that cage!
You!
But, well, um, just asking,
but are your octopus friends?
As yummy as everyone
says they are why don't
you think with your head
instead of your stomach?
What a moron hey wait
a second does this mean
that you guys know hot
chin he must be like
an Old friend of yours or something he's
not our friend at all
no turn the ship around
Sorry we can't help you
i know we said yes at
first but we didn't
know this was the friend
You were talking about
oh come on you can't just
leave him like this
after coming all this way
Please don't worry about
it Kuma just leave okay
this is a trap this sucks
fine then i'll have to
Do it i'm
in i never
would have thought you guys
would turn out to be such
a bunch of heartless?
Morons! Morons! Morons! Oh, shut up!
Just hang on, Hachi!
I promise you, we won't
leave this place without you!
Here we come!
We got you now, Amy!
You've gotta be kidding me!
That's just pathetic!
Now we're all gonna be filthy rich!
Especially since the only
guy who ever saves you, kid!
You're not gonna escape
from us this time, Amy!
It's over!
Why didn't you just run away? Kuma!
Papagoo!
Bastards.
Kuma hasn't done anything.
Sanji, hold on a second, okay?
All right.
We might as well save him after all.
Sanji isn't all that bad.
I'd go so far as to say he's harmless.
I'm not gonna hold a grudge.
And besides, we promised Kuma
we'd help her, didn't we?
Oh!
Oh, Nami!
I love when you're firm, but I
love when you're forgiving, too!
Are you sure, Nami?
It's really okay.
Yep.
Right, Luffy?
If you say it's okay, it's okay.
We'll save the octopus. Look!
His eyes are octopus fritters!
Are the preparations in order?
Flying fish riders.
Of course, we're always ready!
Time for Gump Gump!
Pistons!
You leave them alone!
He's got Devil Fruit power!
Straw head?
Damn, that little bump!
Thank you, Loopy!
You saved us! Yeah!
I got him, octopus!
Thank you, Straw Hat.
You have my most sincere
gratitude for saving little Kuma.
I owe you one. Hey!
Cut up the octopus's
cage and untie him, Zoro!
Right.
Be careful, Straw Hat.
The trap is still set.
The Flying Fish Riders
have got you surrounded.
They'll take you down any way they can.
Don't let your guard down.
Now attack.
Sir!
You're the greatest.
I don't care if they
come from the sea or sky.
We'll be ready.
We're gonna beat the crap out of them
Damn it quick while we
still have the chance.
Come on.
Let's go get Kuma back There.
Kuma, Pupaku, it's dangerous here.
You need to stand back.
Go, go, get a fish!
Go, go, get him back!
Guys, they're here!
Right.
Let's get it, boys!
Fresh fish delivery!
Let's see, which one do I want?
Okay, that one.
Here, fishy-fishy!
My turn!
Hey!
Ooh, nice ride!
Look up!
I'm flying!
This is bad! What if he falls?
Whatever.
Try some of these!
Uh-oh!
Damn it!
They're gonna sink the ship at this rate!
That was close!
Monks, if they hit a lady with one of
those bombs, then there'll be hell to pay.
Love his tail!
They'll get in the way!
Everyone, dive!
Roger!
Luffy!
Try not to drown!
Ah!
Oh, come on!
We're having a damn fight here!
Don't screw around!
Sorry.
And you two were even worse.
What the hell did you
think was going to happen?
You have Devil Fruit powers.
I was just trying to help.
I'm sorry to have caused you
so much trouble, friends.
In the future,
how about when we're in the
middle of a big dangerous fight,
you don't try to drown
yourselves in the ocean, okay?
Jeez, I should have let you guys sink.
It's the Metro Gang.
Now's our chance.
Get her while the Straw Hats are busy.
Hey guys, stop drowning and get
over here to help us already.
I thought I was going
to be in there forever.
Thanks.
I know we got some bad blood between
us, but you're a great guy, Roronoa.
Sure.
I was just following orders, so... Wait!
You butcher cowards, you used me like
a punching bag while I was tied up.
Do you really think I'm
gonna let that slide?
You want another taste of
my fish bag karate? Fine!
You don't scare me.
Want some? Bring it on!
I admit, it was fun beating on you when
you were tied up and couldn't fight back.
But I ain't picky.
I'll beat on you any way you like.
And if you got any requests,
direct them to my fist.
My sword and my ancient goldfish
fighting style will rip you to pieces,
and the sea will run red with blood.
Take this!
We'll let you go this time.
Punch it!
Jamie! Papagoom!
I'm so glad you're okay! Where are you?
I can't believe I got
captured by those idiots!
I didn't want to put you in danger!
It's fine!
We're all safe now, right?
Watch out!
Hey, stupid!
Did you forget about us already?
If you want your buddy back,
you'll have to go through us!
But good luck with that, because
you're in our territory, pal!
You let your guard down too easily stay
back and leave this to us. Don't worry.
We'll be done here in no time
It's like I owe you again, Roronoa.
I'm so sorry for what I did to you before
Back when we fought I hurt you
pretty bad with my six sword style
Oh, did you?
Because I don't think
you hit me even once.
You?
Oh, I guess not.
All right, Chopper, line it up.
Let's see how they like this. Fire!
See that?
Three in one shot! Bullseye!
That was awesome!
Any of you men got the
balls to do a zero fight?
A zero fight?
Interesting, but I don't know
if I'm up for the broken bones.
Does that mean you're going
to pay the medical bills?
How does a million berries sound?
Ah!
I'll do it, head!
Step back, boys!
This is how it's done!
Some big guy's coming right at us!
He's got a huge club!
Yeah, and looks like he's not steering.
Don't tell me the lunatic's trying
to crash straight into our ship.
With that size and speed,
he'll end up sinking us.
Luffy, you get the fish, okay?
Yeah, no Bear Get ready!
If you think you can stop
me, go ahead and try.
But I'm slamming into you either way.
Sanji's right.
He's not turning away.
No problem.
Sure, he's fast, but if he flies into me.
He's done for.
Gump gump below.
I know what we're having for
dinner. Oh, wow! It's huge!
It sure could have caused a lot of damage.
Damn, these pirates are
putting up one hell of a fight.
Who would have thought?
Ufa!
There sure are a lot of those guys.
That's annoying.
How many of them do you think we have
to beat before they just give up?
Ah!
I want to ride! What?!
Don't think I'm gonna stop trying
because of what happened last time!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not swimming after you again!
How devastating.
Come on, Brooke.
What's wrong?
To think that in my first battle as a
member of the crew, all I did was drown.
If I cannot right this wrong,
how can I call myself a man?
I wonder how many I can strike down.
I am of meager talent,
but I shall do my best!
Stand back and observe.
What's with the weird skeleton mask?
I'll run him straight through!
You, too!
Music is power!
Come on!
I fell asleep!
What the hell kind of move was that?
I don't know, but whatever
it was, it was a dirty trick.
It wasn't a trick at all, sir.
It was music!
Get back here! Not bad!
It's like fun, too.
I gotta step things up.
Oh, no, not again.
Loopy, come back!
Now I got you.
Hey, don't die.
I'll smash your head in.
Are you kidding?
He's asleep?
Wake up, we're gonna crash!
That punk, he crashed
straight into the heads room.
You saw, didn't you?
No way!
A familiar face, huh?